(Sheldon:)But, um, I did have you.
And every day at 4:00,
you'd come to my house on Channel 68...
(Sheldon:)...and we'd do science together.
(Sheldon:)If it hadn't been for you, well, who knows
what would have become of me, you know?
(Sheldon:)Instead of a world-class physicist,
I could've wound up as a hobo...
(Sheldon:)...or a surgeon.
(Leonard:)I bet there are important discoveries
being made every day...
(Leonard:)...because you inspired millions of kids
to pursue science.
(Leonard:)In a way, their discoveries
are your discoveries.
(Sheldon:)It's true. A generation of young scientists
are standing on your shoulders.
Well, thank you, guys. That means a lot.
Well, it's important you know
how much you mean to us.
- Uh-oh.
- Arthur, are you okay?
(Arthur:)I'm having...
(Arthur:)...a problem with my pacemaker.